onlineeducation.net 2019-06-11

# Education Database Online : Privacy Policy

**Terms of Use and Privacy Policy for Use of OnlineEducation.net (Effective January 25, 2016)**

Thank you for reading and using our website's content and services. The policy laid out below explains the conditions under which you may use our website, and the way in which OnlineEducation.net gathers and uses information to provide content and related products and services to visitors. By using OnlineEducation.net, you are explicitly agreeing to our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.

Generally we gather two types of information:

  1. **Submitted information:**
    1. In order to provide the services requested of us by our visitors, we distribute web forms that allow visitors to voluntarily and willingly share personal contact information (including their name, phone number, personal address and email address), as well any additional information needed to match you with our other education products or services. We collect, store, and share this information with schools and approved third parties in order to distribute material pertaining to schools, programs and education related services. 
    2. Submitting this information explicitly authorizes OnlineEducation.net, and our affiliated schools and partners, to contact you in accordance with all applicable laws by telephone, text messages, email or mail regarding education opportunities or similar topics. If you receive email from OnlineEducation.net, a school, or a third party, you will be permitted to unsubscribe through a link in the body of your email, at which point you will no longer receive email from that specific sender. 
  2. **Automatic information:**
    1. As is the case with many websites, we also receive and record certain types of anonymous information whenever you interact with OnlineEducation.net. This information helps us make improvements to our site helps us create a more relevant experience for our visitors. As an example, we use “cookies” to collect anonymous information for our web analytics team, site optimization and for tailored advertising and marketing purposes. A partial list of the type of information we collect includes your browser, operating system, and IP address. Continue reading for more information about how we use cookies. 

In using OnlineEducation.net, you acknowledge and agree that information collected on our website may be shared with schools, affiliated companies, and third parties to bring you information regarding degrees, college programs, and other education-related products and services. You also acknowledge and confirm that we retain the right to disseminate any of the information we gather, including identification information, as needed, to businesses providing our company with administrative services.

By submitting your information to OnlineEducation.net, you are granting permission to us and all of our affiliates to contact you, over the phone or via text messages, email, or mail to provide information, including marketing material, for education related products and services. Additionally, submitting your information also grants us, our affiliates, partners, and vendors the express right to contact you for a period of time, effectively relinquishing any rights granted to you by the Do Not Call list or a related applicable law. Effectively, your submission is an omission to Do Not Call requirements established by local, state, and federal governments. This may exempt us from other applicable laws.

We further have the right to release your personal information in instances required by law, for example to abide by a subpoena or other legal action, when, in good faith, we feel we need to preserve our rights, ensure your safety or the security of others, explore alleged fraud, reply to a government or legal request, and/or in the case that OnlineEducation.net is merging, acquisitioning, or selling some or all of its assets.

## Terms of Use and Privacy Policy Notification

We reserve the right to revise our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy in the event that we change our practices. We recommend that you reread this information periodically to remain abreast of our practices regarding your privacy and contact information.

## Cookie Policy – a part of our Privacy Policy

By using this website, you explicitly recognize that we use Cookies and you explicitly consent to our use of cookies.

Cookies are small chunks of information sent from a website and stored in a user’s web browser, including for technical purposes, such as web analytics. Our web analytics are primarily pulled from Google Analytics, a tool provided by Google, Inc. Advertising cookies do not contain personally identifiable information, allowing users to remain anonymous, but cookies do allow advertisers to display ads relevant to the user’s interests and search history. These cookies are often referred to as third-party cookies, since they track navigation and promote ads on behalf of third parties.

To learn more about Google Analytics, you can view Google’s privacy policy at http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html.

Below are examples of how Cookies can be used by us, including services and agreements with vendors and third party services:

  * Web analytics, including demographic and other anonymous information for web optimization and other analysis
  * “Lead auditing” to ensure the accuracy, relevance and validity of submitted information
  * Marketing and conversion tracking cookies. Uses include, but are not confined to, targeting and improving digital ad serving to optimize relevance, your experience, and advertising efficacy

You may remove cookies in your browser settings at any point. You might need to do this each time you use OnlineEducation.net.

You may further opt-out of getting personalized ads from third party advertisers and ad networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) or who follow the Digital Advertising Alliance's Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising by opting out on the NAI and DAA websites.

If you have questions or concerns about our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy, please consult our contact page.
